<package>
 <shortname>Alfresco CMIS AtomPub Binding</shortname>
 <description>
 <![CDATA[
 The Content Management Interoperability Services (CMIS) standard defines a domain model and set of bindings that include Web Services and ReSTful AtomPub that
 can be used by applications to work with one or more Content Management repositories/systems. The CMIS interface is designed to be layered on top of existing 
 Content Management systems and their existing programmatic interfaces. It is not intended to prescribe how specific features should be implemented within those 
 CM systems, nor to exhaustively expose all of the CM system’s capabilities through the CMIS interfaces. Rather, it is intended to define a generic/universal set
 of capabilities provided by a CM system and a set of services for working with those capabilities.
 <p/>
 For a full description of the domain model and binding see the <a href="http://www.oasis-open.org/committees/document.php?document_id=36412">CMIS specification</a>.
 <p/>
 This Web Scripts package provides the Alfresco implementation of the CMIS AtomPub binding. This binding is based upon the Atom (RFC4287) and Atom Publishing Protocol (RFC5023).
 In this binding, the client interacts with the repository by acquiring the service document, which Alfresco provides with each repository installation at:
 <p/>
 http://[host]:[port]/alfresco/service/cmis
 <p/>
 The client will then choose a CMIS collection, and then start accessing the repository by following the references in the returned documents. This binding consists of a service
 document specifying at least CMIS service collections, atom collections, feeds and entry documents. CMIS extends the Atom and AtomPub documents utilizing the Atom and AtomPub
 extension mechanism. CMIS also leverages link tags to specify additional resources related to the requested resource.
 ]]>
 </description>
 <resources>
 
  <resource>
   <shortname>Service Document</shortname>
   <description>Entry point for accessing CMIS AtomPub binding.</description>
   <webscripts>cmis.get</webscripts>
  </resource>
 
  <resource>
   <shortname>Types Collection</shortname>
   <description>Represents a collection of CMIS Type definitions.</description>
   <webscripts>typechildren.get</webscripts>
  </resource>

  <resource>
   <shortname>Types Descendants</shortname>
   <description>Represents a hierarchy of CMIS Type definitions.</description>
   <webscripts>typedescendants.get</webscripts>
  </resource>

  <resource>
   <shortname>Type Description</shortname>
   <description>A CMIS Type Definition</description>
   <webscripts>type.get</webscripts>
  </resource>

  <resource>
   <shortname>CMIS ACLs</shortname>
   <description>Access Control List</description>
   <webscripts>acl.get,acl.put</webscripts>
  </resource>
  
 </resources>
 
</package>