<webscript>
  <shortname>Checked-out Documents (getCheckedoutDocuments)</shortname>
  <description>
<![CDATA[
Gets the list of documents that are checked out that the user has access to.  Most likely this will be the set of documents checked out by the user.  Content-streams are not returned.<br>
<br>
Inputs:<br>
<br>
(Optional) ID folderId<br>
(Optional) String filter specifying which properties to return.<br>
(Optional) Boolean includeAllowableActions: False (default)<br>
(Optional) Enum includeRelationships: none (default), source, target, both<br>
(Optional) int maxItems: 0 = Repository-default number of items (Default)<br>
(Optional) int skipCount: 0 (Default)<br>
<br>
Outputs:<br>
<br>
Result set specified by Filter<br>
Bool hasMoreItems<br>
<br>
Notes:<br>
<br>
The documents will be returned in a repository-specific order.<br>
The repository may include checked-out objects that the calling user has access to, but did not check out.<br>
If folderId is specified, then the results MUST include only the children of that folder, NOT other descendants of the folder nor documents outside this tree.<br>
If “includeAllowableActions” is TRUE, the repository will return the allowable actions for the current user for each document as part of the output.<br>
"IncludeRelationships" indicates whether relationships are also returned for each returned object. If it is set to "source" or "target", relationships for which the returned object is a source, or respectively a target, will also be returned. If it is set to "both", relationships for which the returned object is either a source or a target will be returned. If it is set to "none", relationships are not returned.<br>
If no “maxItems” value is provided, then the Repository will determine an appropriate number of items to return. How the Repository determines this value is repository-specific and opaque to CMIS.<br>    
]]>  
  </description>
  <url>/cmis/checkedout?folderId={folderId?}&amp;includeDescendants={includeDescendants?}&amp;filter={filter?}&amp;skipCount={skipCount?}&amp;maxItems={maxItems?}&amp;includeAllowableActions={includeAllowableActions?}</url>
  <authentication>user</authentication>
  <transaction allow="readonly"/>
  <format default="atomfeed"/>
  <family>CMIS</family>
</webscript>