<webscript>
  <shortname>Create folder or document (createDocument, createFolder)</shortname>
  <description>
<![CDATA[
Creates a document object of the specified type, and optionally adds the document to a folder<br>
<br>
Inputs:<br>
<br>
ID typeId: Document type<br>
Collection properties<br>
(Optional) ID folderId: Parent folder for this new document<br>
(Optional) ContentStream contentStream<br>
(Optional) Enum versioningState: CheckedOut, CheckedInMinor, CheckedInMajor (Default)<br>
<br>
Outputs:<br> 
<br>
ID objectId: Id of the created document object<br>
<br>
The versioningState input is used to create a document in a checked-out state, or as a checked-in minor version, or as a checked-in major version. If created in a checked-out state, the object is a PWC and there is no corresponding "checked out document". (See the "Versioning" section.)<br>
If the Document’s Object Type does not allow content-stream and a content-stream is provided, or if content-stream is required and a content-stream is not provided, throw ConstraintViolationException.<br>
If a Folder is specified, and the Document’s Object Type is not one of the “Allowed_Child_Object_Types” for this Folder, throw ConstraintViolationException.<br>
If unfiling is not supported and a Folder is not specified, throw FolderNotValidException.<br>
Repositories MAY reject the createDocument request (by throwing ConstaintViolationException) if any of the Required properties specified in the Document’s Object Type are not set.<br>
However, iF the repository does NOT reject the createDocument request in this case, the repository MUST leave the newly-created Document in a checked-out state, and MUST ensure that all required properties are set before the Document is checked in.<br>
<br>
<br>
Creates a folder object of the specified type<br>
<br>
Inputs:<br>
<br>
ID typeId: Folder type<br>
Collection properties<br>
ID folderId: Parent folder for this new folder<br>
<br>
Outputs:<br>
<br>
ID objectId: Id of the created folder object<br>
<br>
Notes:<br>
If the to-be-created Folder’s Object Type is not one of the “Allowed_Child_Object_Types” for the parent Folder, throw ConstraintViolationException.<br>
Root folder can not be created using this service.<br>
]]>
  </description>
  
  <url>/cmis/i/{id}/children?sourceFolderId={sourceFolderId}</url>
  <url>/cmis/s/{store}/i/{id}/children?sourceFolderId={sourceFolderId}</url>
  <!-- by path -->
  <url>/cmis/p{path}/children?sourceFolderId={sourceFolderId}</url>
  <url>/cmis/s/{store}/p{path}/children?sourceFolderId={sourceFolderId}</url>
  <!-- alfresco style -->
  <url>/api/node/{store_type}/{store_id}/{id}/children?sourceFolderId={sourceFolderId}</url>
  <url>/api/path/{store_type}/{store_id}/{path}/children?sourceFolderId={sourceFolderId}</url>
  
  <authentication>user</authentication>
  <format default="atomentry"/>
  <family>CMIS</family>
</webscript>